speedmystream.net 2014-06-25

# Speed My Stream

## Privacy Policy

This privacy statement describes how Speedmystream collects and uses the personal information you provide on our Web site: Speedmystream.com It also describes the choices available to you regarding our use of your personal information and how you can access and update this information.

### Collection and Use of Personal Information

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the type of browser you used to visit our site (such as Google Chrome, Internet Explorer or Mozilla Firefox), the time at which you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

We may collect personal information at various times when you use our website. The more information you volunteer (and the more accurate it is), the better we are able to customize your experience. Your participation is voluntary and you have the choice not to disclose any information that we request.

#### The types of information we gather:

  * **Information you provide:** We receive and store any information you enter on speedmystream.com or give us in any other way. You provide most such information when you use the Speedmystream site during the speed test and registration process, which can include demographic information such country or browser. Demographic information may be correlated to web usage information collected during your use of the service.
  * **Automatic information we collect from the site:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our site. For example, like many websites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses the Site, when you use the speed test process, or when you view advertisements and other content served by or on behalf of Licensor on other Web sites. Examples of the information we may collect and analyze when you use our website include the IP address used to connect your computer to the Internet; computer and connection information such as browser type, version, and time zone setting, and browser type, and operating system, including date and time; cookie; web pages you viewed or searched for. During some visits to the Site we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page.

We do not only collect any identifiable information in order to optimize and improve our website.

If you are not yet 18, you are not allowed to use our services. Further, if we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under age 13, we will delete that information as quickly as possible. If you believe that we might have any information from a child under age 13, please contact us.

### Information Sharing

We do not sell your personal information to third parties. However, we may disclose your personal information:

  * As required by law such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process
  * When we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request
  * If speedmystream is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information
  * To any other third party with your prior consent to do so

#### Use of Information

speedmystream may use information (whether personal identifying information or not) that we collect about you to:

  * Deliver the products and services that you have requested
  * Send you offers that you have opted in to receive
  * Manage your relationship with us and provide you with customer support
  * Perform research and analysis about your use of, or interest in, our products, services or content, or products, services or content offered by others
  * Develop and display content and advertising (such as targeted ads) tailored to your interests on our websites and other websites
  * Verify your eligibility and deliver prizes in connection with promotions, contests and sweepstakes
  * Enforce our Agreement
  * Cooperate with legal, criminal or regulatory investigations or proceedings
  * Manage our business
  * Perform functions as otherwise described to you at the time of information collection

### Use of Cookies and Web Beacons

In computer language, a cookie is used to store data on a computer's hard drive. Almost all websites utilize cookies to one extent or another.

We use third-party cookies, known as "web beacons", to advertise our website using a technology known as Retargeting. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies. Certain third party advertisers may collect personal information you provide in fields and forms presented in connection with their ads. This policy does not apply to, and we are not responsible for information you choose to provide in connection with these third party ads. We encourage you to check the privacy policies of the advertisers to learn about their use of your information.

#### Links to Other Web Sites

Our Site includes links to other Web sites whose privacy practices may differ from those of speedmystream. Our service may also be linked to sites or services operated by the speedmystream affiliates or third parties, and may carry advertisements or offer content, functionality, games, rewards programs, newsletters, contests or sweepstakes, or applications developed and maintained by third parties including, any online store. speedmystream is not responsible for the privacy practices of any such third parties, and once you leave the Services via a link, enable a third party service, or click an advertisement, you should check the applicable privacy policy of the third party site. If you submit personal information to any of those sites, your information is governed by their privacy statements. We encourage you to carefully read the privacy statement of any Web site you visit.

### Security

When we collect personal information directly from you, we follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us.

In order to make a purchase from us, you must use our shopping cart provider to finalize and pay for your order. Its privacy statement and security practices will also apply to your information. We encourage you to read that privacy statement before providing your information.

### Notification of Privacy Statement Changes

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

### Contact Information

You can contact us about this privacy statement by emailing us at: [support@speedmystream.com](mailto:support@speedmystream.com).
